export interface Question {
	id: number;
	lectureNo: number;
	questionHeader: string;
	question: string;
	choices?: string[];
	answer: string;
	hint: string;
	slideNo: number;
	solved: boolean;
}
//! get the slide number for all ("sildeNo: 0 or -1")
//! search for all fixme
export const defaultLectureQuestions: Question[] = [
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with key Term(s):',
		question:
			'Problems identified when team members do not follow applicable standards, recorded processes, or procedures ',
		answer: 'Noncompliance issues',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 37,
		solved: false,
		id: 0,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with key Term(s):',
		question:
			'Quality assurance process to develop processes to reduce defects by avoiding or correcting ',
		answer: 'Poka-Yoke',
		hint: 'avoiding or correcting',
		slideNo: 33,
		solved: false,
		id: 1,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with key Term(s):',
		question:
			'Proven set of global best practices that drives business performance through benchmark key capabilities ',
		answer: 'Capability Maturity Model Integration (CMMI)®',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 23,
		solved: false,
		id: 2,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with key Term(s):',
		question:
			"Ongoing process that ensures software product meets and complies with organization's established and standardized quality specifications",
		answer: 'Software quality assurance (SQA)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 8,
		solved: false,
		id: 3,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with key Term(s):',
		question:
			'Tangible resources used by an organization to guide the management of its projects and operations',
		answer: 'Organizational process assets',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 43,
		solved: false,
		id: 4,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with key Term(s):',
		question: 'A process-level improvement training and appraisal program',
		answer: '',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 5,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with key Term(s):',
		question:
			'Proven set of global best practices that drives business performance through building and benchmarking key capabilities',
		answer: 'Capability Maturity Model Integration (CMMI)®',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 21,
		solved: false,
		id: 6,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question:
			'Compare QA and QC in respect of focus and assessment measures/tools.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 15,
		solved: false,
		id: 7,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question:
			'Objectivity in process quality assurance evaluations is critical to success of project. List four objective evaluation methods.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 32,
		solved: false,
		id: 8,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: 'Mention four benefits of software quality assurance.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below and one after it)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 12,
		solved: false,
		id: 9,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: 'Explain what is meant by PDCA/Deming cycle.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 11,
		solved: false,
		id: 10,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question:
			'An agile project using Scrum has many opportunities to objectively evaluate ceremonies and work products. Describe three opportunities.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 39,
		solved: false,
		id: 11,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question:
			'Process tailoring is a critical activity that allows controlled changes to the processes due to the specific needs of a project or a part of the organization. Mention three reasons for process tailoring. ',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 51,
		solved: false,
		id: 12,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: 'List four examples of organizational process assets.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 43,
		solved: false,
		id: 13,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: 'Identify three similarities between QA and QC.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 16,
		solved: false,
		id: 14,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 1,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: 'Mention three quality assurance work products.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 36,
		solved: false,
		id: 15,
	},
	//? LECTURE 2
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with Key Term(s)',
		question:
			'Cost incurred when a product fails to conform to quality specification before shipment to a customer.',
		answer: 'INTERNAL FAILURE COST',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 60,
		solved: false,
		id: 16,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with Key Term(s)',
		question:
			'Principle that states that 80% of effects come from 20% of causes.',
		answer: 'PARETO PRINCIPLE',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 27,
		solved: false,
		id: 17,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with Key Term(s)',
		question:
			'Management meeting at planned intervals to ensure the company quality management system’s continuous suitability, adequacy and alignment with the strategic direction of the organization.',
		answer: 'MANAGEMENT REVIEWS',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 42,
		solved: false,
		id: 18,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with Key Term(s)',
		question:
			'Method for calculating the costs companies incur ensuring that products meet quality standards, as well as the costs of producing goods that fail to meet quality standards.',
		answer: 'COQ ',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 59,
		solved: false,
		id: 19,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with Key Term(s)',
		question:
			'Organization conduct examination at planned intervals to check if quality management system conforms to requirements of International Standard and effectively implemented & maintained.',
		answer: 'INTERNAL AUDITS ',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 39,
		solved: false,
		id: 20,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with Key Term(s)',
		question:
			'Percentage of an organizations total capacity or effort that is being used to overcome the cost of poor quality.',
		answer: 'Hidden Quality Costs (HIDDEN FACTORY)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 64,
		solved: false,
		id: 21,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with Key Term(s)',
		question: 'Matrix that shows how each person contributes to a project.',
		answer: 'RACI',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 54,
		solved: false,
		id: 22,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Replace with Key Term(s)',
		question:
			'A mechanism of analysing the defects to identify their sources.',
		answer: 'RCA',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 8,
		solved: false,
		id: 23,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Identify root cause analysis tool:',
		question:
			'Visual representations of a relationship between two sets of data to test correlation between variables.',
		answer: 'SCATTER PLOT',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 24,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Identify root cause analysis tool:',
		question:
			'Includes a severity occurrence and detection rating to calculate risk and determine the next steps.',
		answer: 'FMEA',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 25,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Identify root cause analysis tool:',
		question:
			'Looking at any problem and drilling down by asking questions and avoid answers that are too simple or overlook important details.',
		answer: '5 WHYS',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 26,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Identify root cause analysis tool:',
		question:
			'Every contributing cause and its potential effects can be shown under categories and sub-categories.',
		answer: 'FISHBONE ',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 27,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Identify root cause analysis tool:',
		question:
			'Bar graph that groups the frequency distribution to show the relative significance of causes of failure.',
		answer: 'PARETO CHART ',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 28,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Identify root cause analysis tool:',
		question:
			'Group activity to collect different viewpoints encouraging a deeper level of critical thinking.',
		answer: 'BRAINSTORMING',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 29,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Identify type of root cause:',
		question: 'Picking the wrong person for a task.',
		answer: 'Organizational',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 30,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Identify type of root cause:',
		question: 'The server is not booting up.',
		answer: 'Physical',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 31,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Identify type of root cause:',
		question: 'Instructions not accurately followed.',
		answer: 'Human',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 32,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Identify PDCA Phase:',
		question: 'Incorporate your plan on a small scale .',
		answer: 'Do',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 33,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Identify PDCA Phase:',
		question: 'Identify resource needs.',
		answer: 'Plan',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 34,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Identify PDCA Phase:',
		question: 'PDCA model becomes the new standard baseline. ',
		answer: 'Act',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 35,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Identify PDCA Phase:',
		question: "Audit your plan's execution.",
		answer: 'Check',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 36,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'MCQ:',
		question:
			'The outputs of the management reviews shall include decisions and actions related to all following, except:',
		choices: [
			'a. opportunities for improvement',
			'b. need for changes to quality management system',
			'c. audit results ',
			'd. resource needs',
		],
		answer: 'c. audit results',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 37,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'MCQ:',
		question: 'Which of the following is not included in action plan?',
		choices: [
			'a. affected stakeholders',
			'c. expected cost',
			'b. schedule',
			'd. results achieved',
		],
		answer: 'd. results achieved',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 38,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Specify Cost Type',
		question: 'Periodic review of documentation',
		answer: 'Appraisal cost',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 39,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Specify Cost Type',
		question: 'Client complaints ',
		answer: 'External failure cost',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 40,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Specify Cost Type',
		question: 'Design verification',
		answer: 'Prevention cost',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 41,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Specify Cost Type',
		question: 'Defective products, before shipment to client',
		answer: 'Internal failure cost',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 42,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Specify Cost Type',
		question: 'New employee training',
		answer: 'Prevention cost',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 43,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Specify Cost Type',
		question: 'Internal auditing ',
		answer: 'Appraisal cost',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 44,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question:
			'The aim of 5 whys root cause analysis is to find the main technical causes  behind the problem. Comment.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 17,
		solved: false,
		id: 45,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question:
			'When to perform causal analysis? Which factors affect decision of effort and formality required?',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 7,
		solved: false,
		id: 46,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: 'Identify elements of process improvement proposal.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 34,
		solved: false,
		id: 47,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: 'Discuss advantages of PCDA approach.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 49,
		solved: false,
		id: 48,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question:
			'Defining the problem is an important step in root cause analysis. Explain the rule that should be followed in defining the problem.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 14,
		solved: false,
		id: 49,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: 'Describe four types of costs of quality.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 60,
		solved: false,
		id: 50,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: 'Identify steps of internal audit process.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 40,
		solved: false,
		id: 51,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: 'Explain roles in RACI model.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 54,
		solved: false,
		id: 52,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 2,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question:
			'List three benefits and limitations of cost of quality system. ',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 63,
		solved: false,
		id: 53,
	},
	//? Lecture 3
	{
		question: 'Static review objectives include ---, ---, and ---.',
		answer: 'finding defects, gaining understanding and educating participants',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Complete:',
		id: 54,
	},
	{
		question:
			'It is very useful that test basis has measurable coverage criteria  to be used as ---. ',
		answer: 'KEY PERFORMANCE INDICATOR (KPI)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Complete:',
		id: 55,
	},
	{
		question:
			'An element of human psychology called --- makes it difficult to accept information that disagrees with currently held beliefs.',
		answer: 'CONFIRMATION BIAS ',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Complete:',
		id: 56,
	},
	{
		question: 'Static testing types include ---, ---, ---, and ---.',
		answer: 'Peer Review, Walkthrough, Technical review, Inspection',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Complete:',
		id: 57,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Acceptance testing of system by administration staff is usually performed in a ---.',
		answer: 'PRODUCTION ENVIRONMENT',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Complete:',
		id: 58,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Finding defects is not the main focus of --- testing, its goal is to build confidence in the software.',
		answer: 'USER ACCEPTANCE',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Complete:',
		id: 59,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Maintenance testing involve planned releases and unplanned releases called ---. ',
		answer: '(HOT FIXES)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Complete:',
		id: 60,
	},
	{
		question: 'Triggers for software maintenance include ---, --- and ---.',
		answer: 'modification, migration and retirement',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Complete:',
		id: 61,
	},
	{
		question:
			'--- testing is used by developers of commercial off-the-shelf (COTS) software who want to get feedback from potential/existing users, customers before the software product is put on the market.',
		answer: 'ALPHA AND BETA',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Complete:',
		id: 62,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Evaluating the review findings against the exit criteria to make a review decision',
		answer: 'Review meeting/issue communication and analysis',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Specify Formal Review/Inspection Activity',
		id: 63,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Explaining the scope, objectives, process, roles, and work products to the participants ',
		answer: 'Initiate review',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Specify Formal Review/Inspection Activity',
		id: 64,
	},
	{
		question: 'Noting potential defects, recommendations, and questions ',
		answer: 'Individual preparation',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Specify Formal Review/Inspection Activity',
		id: 65,
	},
	{
		question: 'Defining the entry and exit criteria',
		answer: 'Planning',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Specify Formal Review/Inspection Activity',
		id: 66,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Document all the issues, problems, and open points that were identified during the meeting. With the advent of tools to support the review process, especially logging of defects/open points/decisions there is often no need for a scribe.',
		answer: 'scribe',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Whose Responsibility in Review?',
		id: 67,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Decide on the execution of reviews, allocates time in project schedules and determines if the review objectives have been met.',
		answer: 'manager',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Whose Responsibility in Review?',
		id: 68,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Lead, plan and run the review. May mediate between the various points of view and is often the person upon whom the success of the review rests.',
		answer: 'moderator/facilitator',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Whose Responsibility in Review?',
		id: 69,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Reviewers are provided with structured guidelines on how to read through the work product based on its expected usage. ',
		answer: 'Scenario-based/dry run.',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Specify Review Technique',
		id: 70,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Reviewers detect issues based on set of questions based on potential defects, which may be derived from experience. ',
		answer: 'Checklist-based.',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Specify Review Technique',
		id: 71,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Reviewers are provided with little or no guidance on how this task should be performed. It needs little preparation and is highly dependent on reviewer skills.',
		answer: 'Ad hoc.',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Specify Review Technique',
		id: 72,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Reviewers take on different stakeholder viewpoints in individual reviewing.',
		answer: 'Perspective-based reading.',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Specify Review Technique',
		id: 73,
	},
	{
		question: 'Incorrect sequencing or timing of interface calls',
		answer: 'Integration testing',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'In Which Testing Level Can Defect be Found?',
		id: 74,
	},
	{
		question: 'Incorrect in code logic',
		answer: 'Component testing',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'In Which Testing Level Can Defect be Found?',
		id: 75,
	},
	{
		question:
			'Failure of the system to work properly in the production environment(s)',
		answer: 'System testing',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'In Which Testing Level Can Defect be Found?',
		id: 76,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: 'Explain the testing principles in details.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 7,
		solved: false,
		id: 77,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question:
			'Identify three guidelines to successful conduct of review process.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 22,
		solved: false,
		id: 78,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: 'Clarify the tester role during each of SDLC phases.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 13,
		solved: false,
		id: 79,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question:
			'What should a tester do in case a component is not finished and he needs to conduct component integration testing?',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 45,
		solved: false,
		id: 80,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: 'Compare between regression and confirmation testing types.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 61,
		solved: false,
		id: 81,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 3,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: 'Illustrate steps of dynamic testing using a diagram.',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 40,
		solved: false,
		id: 82,
	},
	//? Lecture 4
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader: 'Identify testing estimation technique',
		question:
			'Breaking down the test project into modules; sub-modules; functionalities; tasks and estimate effort/duration for each task .',
		answer: 'WORK BREAKDOWN STRUCTURE (WBS)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 83,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader: 'Identify testing estimation technique',
		question:
			'Assumes that you already tested similar applications in previous projects and collected metrics from those projects.',
		answer: 'EXPERIANCED-BASED TESTING',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 84,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader: 'Identify testing estimation technique',
		question:
			'Three types of estimations most likely/optimistic/pessimistic are calculated for each activity.',
		answer: '(PERT) ',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 85,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader: 'Identify testing estimation technique',
		question:
			'Work breakdown structure is distributed to a team comprising of 3-7 members for re-estimating the tasks and final estimate is the result of the summarized estimates based on the team agreement.',
		answer: 'WIDE-BAND DELPHI',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 86,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader: 'Identify Test Strategy Type',
		question:
			'Tests rely on making systematic use of predefined set of tests/test conditions, such as taxonomy of common types of failures, list of important quality characteristics, or company-wide look-and-feel standards.',
		answer: 'METHODICAL',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 87,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader: 'Identify Test Strategy Type',
		question:
			'Tests are designed and implemented, and may immediately be executed in response to knowledge gained from prior test results rather than being pre-planned.',
		answer: 'REACTIVE',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 88,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader: 'Identify Test Strategy Type',
		question:
			'Tests are designed based on some required aspect of the product, such as function, business process, internal structure, non-functional characteristic.',
		answer: 'MODEL BASED',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 89,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader: 'Identify Test Strategy Type',
		question:
			'Tests include reuse of existing test ware (especially test cases and test data) and test suites.',
		answer: 'REGRESSION-AVERSE',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 90,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader: 'Identify Test Strategy Type',
		question:
			'Tests driven primarily by the advice, guidance, or instructions of stakeholders, business domain experts, or technology experts, who may be outside the test team or outside the organization itself.',
		answer: 'DIRECTED (consultative)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 91,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: '',
		answer: '(Open the 6 slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 4,
		solved: false,
		id: 92,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: '',
		answer: '(Open the 2 slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 22,
		solved: false,
		id: 93,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: '',
		answer: '(Open the 3 slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 31,
		solved: false,
		id: 94,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: '',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 37,
		solved: false,
		id: 95,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader: 'Exercise:',
		question: '',
		answer: '(Open the slide(s) from below)',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: 59,
		solved: false,
		id: 96,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader:
			'Specify scenario severity (high/low) and priority (high/low)',
		question:
			'Submit button is not working on a login page and customers are unable to login to the application.',
		answer: 'High Priority & High Severity',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 97,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader:
			'Specify scenario severity (high/low) and priority (high/low)',
		question:
			'Crash in some functionality which is going to deliver after couple of releases.',
		answer: 'Low Priority & High Severity',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 98,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader:
			'Specify scenario severity (high/low) and priority (high/low)',
		question: 'Spelling mistake of a company name on homepage.',
		answer: 'High Priority & Low Severity',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 99,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader:
			'Specify scenario severity (high/low) and priority (high/low)',
		question: 'FAQ page takes a long time to load.',
		answer: 'Low Priority & Low Severity',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 100,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader:
			'Specify scenario severity (high/low) and priority (high/low)',
		question: 'Company logo or tagline issues.',
		answer: 'High Priority & Low Severity',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 101,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader:
			'Specify scenario severity (high/low) and priority (high/low)',
		question:
			'On a bank website, an error message pops up when a customer clicks on transfer money button.',
		answer: 'High Priority & High Severity',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 102,
	},
	{
		lectureNo: 4,
		questionHeader:
			'Specify scenario severity (high/low) and priority (high/low)',
		question:
			'Font family or font size or colour or spelling issue in the application or reports.',
		answer: 'Low Priority & Low Severity',
		hint: '',
		slideNo: -1,
		solved: false,
		id: 103,
	},
];

// lecture x, slide y
const MISSING_QUESTIONS_SLIDES = [];
